<topics>
  <topic number="1">
    <title>claymation kids show with british narrator dog kid penguin in white void</title>
    <description>Nick Jr. claymation show? I have one vague memory of a claymation kid’s show. It had a dog character, possibly a kid character(unsure), and a British narrator. I think it also had a penguin character that had a hat that did some crazy things. Also I think the show always took place in a white void. Don’t get it twisted though, I’m not thinking of that claymation penguin “noot noot” show.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the western tv series Pocoyo.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Pocoyo claymation, Pocoyo claymation western, western animation Pocoyo</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/bnzd3x/tomtkids_show_nick_jr_claymation_show/</redditID>
    
<topics>
  <topic number="2">
    <title>British education video british woman and dog crisp facory</title>
    <description>Hello, I am looking for a video. I remember watching it on tape in school, it was a British woman and her dog that traveled everywhere. In one of the tapes, she traveled to a crisps factory and showed how they made crisps and such. Does anyone know where I can find it? I think the dog's name was ringo or dingo..</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the kids education video Come Outside.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Come Outside, Come Outside education video, british education video Come Outside</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/2cg0rf/tomtmovie_british_education_video/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>


<topics>
  <topic number="3">
    <title>Jackie Chan fight scene using pretzel dough movie</title>
    <description></description>
    <narrative>relevant documents points to or describes the film Mr. Nice Guy</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Mr. Nice Guy, Mr. Nice Guy film, movie Mr. Nice Guy</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/41ph2s/tomt_movie_jackie_chan_fight_scene_using_pretzel/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>


<topics>
  <topic number="4">
    <title>Movie about a paranoid guy who ends of surveilling himself in the meta-climax. Live-action with weird bug-eye style.</title>
    <description>It's not *A Scanner Darkly*, it's more recent. It was on Netflix but now I can't find it. The movie was live-action but they added weird distortion on the bodies so they had big eyes. Anyone remember the title? The guy works in a retro surveillance operation, reminiscent of the technology in *Brazil*. He puts on big headphones and listens (iirc) to people's thoughts.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the Film Waking life.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Waking Life?, waking life movie</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/4ljg8y/tomtmovie_movie_about_a_paranoid_guy_who_ends_of/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

<topics>
  <topic number="5">
    <title>Martial arts movie I saw on TV in the 80s asian country </title>
    <description>This is a martial arts movie I saw on tv back in the 80s.  It was probably around 1985 when I saw it, but since it was on tv the movie itself may have been older than that.The movie took place in an Asian country, likely either Japan or China, and I think the people were wearing traditional Asian clothing so it may have been set in an earlier time period. The scene I remember has a guy fighting multiple other guys, using swords. Eventually he has to run away, and he runs down a large flight of steps in front of a building that may have been a temple. One of the guys he was fighting pushes over a huge cylindrical stone statue and rolls it down the steps after him.  To get away faster the guy lays down and just rolls down the steps.  When he gets about halfway down the steps, the guy's friend or cousin or something jumps out to help him, thinking that he was still fighting humans. Then when he sees the statue rolling towards him he starts rolling down the steps like the first guy, but he doesn't get away and the statue rolls over him. In the next scene, an old woman is talking to a child, telling him or her about the fight, and how the first guy got away, but his friend or cousin died while saving his life.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the Film The synopsis of Executioners of Shaolin.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>The synopsis of Executioners of Shaolin, The synopsis of Executioners of Shaolin film, The synopsis of Executioners of Shaolin material art</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1mb72w/tomtmovie_martial_arts_movie_i_saw_on_tv_in_the/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>


<topics>
  <topic number="6">
    <title>Movie about killer chimpanzees</title>
    <description>I watched it on TV I think about 2005 so it would be older than that. I think it was British, set in a house in the countryside.\n\nIt was about some scientists who had done experiments on 2 chimpanzees, and one of the chimps started trying to kill them.\n\nAt the end one of the scientists escapes and drives away with the second chimp who they think is nice and safe, but then camera pulls back to show it\u2019s killed all the sheep in the paddocks around the house.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the Film Link.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Link film, Link movie</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments//8ltaz2/tomt_movie_about_killer_chimpanzees/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>


    
    
    
  </topic>
  <topic number="20">
    <title>website selling t-shirts bags posters with text of whole book</title>
    <description>I look for a website that sells T-shirts, bags, and posters that had a whole book written on them.</description>
    <narrative>A relevant website allows to buy t-shirts, bags, and posters with a complete book written on it. Highly relevant are documents on the domain litographs.com, relevant are documents that talk about litographs.com or a similar page.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>litographs art from books,litographs.com,litographs t-shirts from books</positiveQueries>
    <tomtUrl>http://www.reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1rg81e/tomt_website/</tomtUrl>
  </topic>
  <topic number="21">
    <title>dutch dystopian webcomic having a white lavender color scheme in a snowy setting</title>
    <description>A Dutch (maybe) Webcomic. A couple of my Dutch-speaking (I'm not even sure about that maybe even Finnish) friends recommended a Webcomic to me on Teamspeak and I remember the first page having a white/lavender color scheme in a snowy setting. I remember something about releasing two or three pages a week but when I saw it on April I believe they took a month break or something. I don't remember the plot, they just told me to read it. I can't get into contact with them anymore so I can't ask but I think the genre was dystopian.</description>
    <narrative></narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Sssscomic.com, stand still stay silent web comic, finnish swedish webcomic stand still stay silent</positiveQueries>
    <tomtUrl>https://www.reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/3c65x0/tomtwebsite_a_dutch_maybe_webcomic/</tomtUrl>
    <falseMemory>finnish swedish not dutch</falseMemory>
  </topic>
  <topic number="22">
    <title>search engine for pictures of a predominant color</title>
    <description>A website where you can pick colors and it gives you a picture of something that is predominantly that color. I think I first saw it on a vsauce3 dong video. Basically you have a color palette arhat you choose from and it gives you a picture or a flower or something that is mostly the color that you choose. Sorry, I basically said the exact same thing over again but I don't know how else to explain it.</description>
    <narrative></narrative>
    <positiveQueries>tineye Multicolr Search by color, tineye multicolor search,  tineye multicolr MulticolorEngine </positiveQueries>
    <tomtUrl>https://www.reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1u1tzm/tomt_website_a_website_where_you_can_pick_colors/</tomtUrl>
  </topic>
</topics>


