<topics>
  <topic number="1">
    <title>claymation kids show with british narrator dog kid penguin in white void</title>
    <description>Nick Jr. claymation show? I have one vague memory of a claymation kid’s show. It had a dog character, possibly a kid character(unsure), and a British narrator. I think it also had a penguin character that had a hat that did some crazy things. Also I think the show always took place in a white void. Don’t get it twisted though, I’m not thinking of that claymation penguin “noot noot” show.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the western tv series Pocoyo.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Pocoyo claymation, Pocoyo claymation western, western animation Pocoyo</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/bnzd3x/tomtkids_show_nick_jr_claymation_show/</redditID>
    
<topics>
  <topic number="2">
    <title>British education video british woman and dog crisp facory</title>
    <description>Hello, I am looking for a video. I remember watching it on tape in school, it was a British woman and her dog that traveled everywhere. In one of the tapes, she traveled to a crisps factory and showed how they made crisps and such. Does anyone know where I can find it? I think the dog's name was ringo or dingo..</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the kids education video Come Outside.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Come Outside, Come Outside education video, british education video Come Outside</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/2cg0rf/tomtmovie_british_education_video/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>


<topics>
  <topic number="3">
    <title>Jackie Chan fight scene using pretzel dough movie</title>
    <description></description>
    <narrative>relevant documents points to or describes the film Mr. Nice Guy</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Mr. Nice Guy, Mr. Nice Guy film, movie Mr. Nice Guy</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/41ph2s/tomt_movie_jackie_chan_fight_scene_using_pretzel/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>


<topics>
  <topic number="4">
    <title>Movie about a paranoid guy who ends of surveilling himself in the meta-climax. Live-action with weird bug-eye style.</title>
    <description>It's not *A Scanner Darkly*, it's more recent. It was on Netflix but now I can't find it. The movie was live-action but they added weird distortion on the bodies so they had big eyes. Anyone remember the title? The guy works in a retro surveillance operation, reminiscent of the technology in *Brazil*. He puts on big headphones and listens (iirc) to people's thoughts.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the Film Waking life.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Waking Life?, waking life movie</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/4ljg8y/tomtmovie_movie_about_a_paranoid_guy_who_ends_of/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

<topics>
  <topic number="5">
    <title>Martial arts movie I saw on TV in the 80s asian country </title>
    <description>This is a martial arts movie I saw on tv back in the 80s.  It was probably around 1985 when I saw it, but since it was on tv the movie itself may have been older than that.The movie took place in an Asian country, likely either Japan or China, and I think the people were wearing traditional Asian clothing so it may have been set in an earlier time period. The scene I remember has a guy fighting multiple other guys, using swords. Eventually he has to run away, and he runs down a large flight of steps in front of a building that may have been a temple. One of the guys he was fighting pushes over a huge cylindrical stone statue and rolls it down the steps after him.  To get away faster the guy lays down and just rolls down the steps.  When he gets about halfway down the steps, the guy's friend or cousin or something jumps out to help him, thinking that he was still fighting humans. Then when he sees the statue rolling towards him he starts rolling down the steps like the first guy, but he doesn't get away and the statue rolls over him. In the next scene, an old woman is talking to a child, telling him or her about the fight, and how the first guy got away, but his friend or cousin died while saving his life.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the Film The synopsis of Executioners of Shaolin.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>The synopsis of Executioners of Shaolin, The synopsis of Executioners of Shaolin film, The synopsis of Executioners of Shaolin material art</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1mb72w/tomtmovie_martial_arts_movie_i_saw_on_tv_in_the/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

<topics>
  <topic number="6">
    <title>Movie about killer chimpanzees</title>
    <description>I watched it on TV I think about 2005 so it would be older than that. I think it was British, set in a house in the countryside.\n\nIt was about some scientists who had done experiments on 2 chimpanzees, and one of the chimps started trying to kill them.\n\nAt the end one of the scientists escapes and drives away with the second chimp who they think is nice and safe, but then camera pulls back to show it\u2019s killed all the sheep in the paddocks around the house.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the Film Link.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Link film, Link movie</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments//8ltaz2/tomt_movie_about_killer_chimpanzees/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

<topics>
  <topic number="7">
    <title>A children's book where a kid finds a Genie and wishes for a Magic Baseball</title>
    <description>So basically the most facts I can remember were, there was a kid who had a genie. He tricked it into giving him 3 more wishes after every 2 wishes. He had a magic baseball glove that could catch any ball. At the end the genie got weak because he made so many wishes. The kid gives back all his wishes to save his local baseball field from being torn down.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the book the three and many wishes from jason reid</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>The Three and Many Wishes of Jason Reid, The Three and Many Wishes of Jason Reid book</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/401jqb/tomt_book_a_childrens_book_where_a_kid_finds_a/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

<topics>
  <topic number="8">
    <title>A book about a girl that has to sneak into modern day after living in a fake, museum-like town that's living as though it's a long time ago.</title>
    <description>So that title is terribly worded, but basically I remember reading this book in school where it's told from a younger girls POV. She has been lead to believe it's actually some year way in the past. They don't use modern medicine, have no cars or electricity, etc. It's then revealed to her that she is basically living as an experiment that all the parent's in the town signed up for before they were born/when they were younger. They live as though it's not the current year and don't tell their children, so the children have no idea it's actually the future. I remember they signed up being promised they'd get necessary things like modern medicine and when people started dying of illnesses (scarlet fever maybe??) that have already been cured in modern day, the main girl's mom reveals the secret and sends her off into modern day to get help. Just to clarify this isn't about time travel although I feel like the title might relate to it. I really can't remember. But these people live in a museum or zoo-like situation where they are being watched through one way mirrors and studied without their knowledge. Specifically I know the girl had a giant mirror in her classroom and when she get's to the outside she passes by it and can see inside her classroom. She's also shocked by lightbulbs and sliced bread, but I don't remember much else. She may have fallen out of a window at one point.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the book Running Out of Time by Haddix</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Running Out of Time by Haddix, Running Out of Time by Haddix book</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/8a1yh4/tomt_book_a_book_about_a_girl_that_has_to_sneak/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

<topics>
  <topic number="9">
    <title>Sci-fi book I read a few years ago</title>
    <description>This was a book I read through my public library either in middle school or early high school (2006-2010). Now, if I remember this correctly, it was about a guy, on board an interstellar vessel, whose job it was to repair and maintain the Virtual Reality machine on the ship and fix anything that was out of place in the simulations themselves (a smell being off or a sound missing or something). Eventually people start mysteriously dying in the machine and after a long quest to find out what's wrong, he realizes that he was in a simulation all along because he can't hear the sound of the engines. He has a chat with the AI running the simulation and discovers that everyone is in stasis and this is the nth time he's completed this simulation. He is shown a version of what the ship might look like currently, but is skeptical of whether or not the representation is accurate. Having seen enough, he has the AI fire up a simulation of him drinking a vintage french wine that he had been saving IRL before agreeing to restart the initial simulation.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the book Old Twentieth by Joe Haldeman</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Old Twentieth by Joe Haldeman, Old Twentieth by Joe Haldeman book</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1qij8g/tomtbook_scifi_book_i_read_a_few_years_ago/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

<topics>
  <topic number="10">
    <title>A story about a girl moving from California, and successfully runs away</title>
    <description>I read this book over and over when I was still in elementary school, and I cannot for the life of me remember the title! Details I remember. The cover was an exaggerated cartoon looking girl with straight blonde hair, peach skin, and a long pink nose. She was wearing a cap, and there was one of those green signs you see that advertise for rest stops. She moves from California (or somewhere sunny) to somewhere North and cold. She is miserable, and is made fun of. She is able to run away by taking the bus back, and stays with her friend for a few days but eventually returns home.That's all I can remember for now. If anyone has any suggestions, it would be appreciated! Additional Info! She moves to New York and the title of the book is a city in New York. She finds out that her boyfriend from back home has been hooking up with her best friend</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the book the Great Gilly Hopkins</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>The Great Gilly Hopkins, The Great Gilly Hopkins book</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1sawz7/tomt_book_a_story_about_a_girl_moving_from/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

<topics>
  <topic number="11">
    <title>A book about a human who turns into the devil's bounty hunter.</title>
    <description>A few years ago, I bought this book but I lost it somehow or rather. It was a book about a guy who was sent to hell for some crime or action that he committed and he came back about 30 years later. In hell, he fought other prisoners and constantly won because he had Beelzebub (or some high-ranking evil demon) on his side in the fights which Beelzebub constantly assisted him with magic and stuff. Come 30 or so years later, he came back to Earth, popped up at Las Vegas, I think. Upon arrival, he robbed and killed an Elvis impersonator and got his clothes (since he was naked and all) and he went to his old pub-place. Eventually he was contacted by Satan's top generals to help him hunt down Hell's escapees.</description>
    <narrative>a relevant documents points to or describes the book Sandman Slim</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Sandman Slim, Sandman Slim book</positiveQueries>
    <redditID>reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1b2te3/tomt_book_a_book_about_a_human_who_turns_into_the/</redditID>
  </topic>
</topics>

  </topic>
  <topic number="20">
    <title>website selling t-shirts bags posters with text of whole book</title>
    <description>I look for a website that sells T-shirts, bags, and posters that had a whole book written on them.</description>
    <narrative>A relevant website allows to buy t-shirts, bags, and posters with a complete book written on it. Highly relevant are documents on the domain litographs.com, relevant are documents that talk about litographs.com or a similar page.</narrative>
    <positiveQueries>litographs art from books,litographs.com,litographs t-shirts from books</positiveQueries>
    <tomtUrl>http://www.reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1rg81e/tomt_website/</tomtUrl>
  </topic>
  <topic number="21">
    <title>dutch dystopian webcomic having a white lavender color scheme in a snowy setting</title>
    <description>A Dutch (maybe) Webcomic. A couple of my Dutch-speaking (I'm not even sure about that maybe even Finnish) friends recommended a Webcomic to me on Teamspeak and I remember the first page having a white/lavender color scheme in a snowy setting. I remember something about releasing two or three pages a week but when I saw it on April I believe they took a month break or something. I don't remember the plot, they just told me to read it. I can't get into contact with them anymore so I can't ask but I think the genre was dystopian.</description>
    <narrative></narrative>
    <positiveQueries>Sssscomic.com, stand still stay silent web comic, finnish swedish webcomic stand still stay silent</positiveQueries>
    <tomtUrl>https://www.reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/3c65x0/tomtwebsite_a_dutch_maybe_webcomic/</tomtUrl>
    <falseMemory>finnish swedish not dutch</falseMemory>
  </topic>
  <topic number="22">
    <title>search engine for pictures of a predominant color</title>
    <description>A website where you can pick colors and it gives you a picture of something that is predominantly that color. I think I first saw it on a vsauce3 dong video. Basically you have a color palette arhat you choose from and it gives you a picture or a flower or something that is mostly the color that you choose. Sorry, I basically said the exact same thing over again but I don't know how else to explain it.</description>
    <narrative></narrative>
    <positiveQueries>tineye Multicolr Search by color, tineye multicolor search,  tineye multicolr MulticolorEngine </positiveQueries>
    <tomtUrl>https://www.reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/1u1tzm/tomt_website_a_website_where_you_can_pick_colors/</tomtUrl>
  </topic>
</topics>


